how
welcome to office hours.
So nice to see all of you here.
It's a smaller group, I think, given our
change in office hours for this week.
But that means we can have a richer
conversation.
Our most recent session covered workforce
and leadership.
But don't feel like you need to limit
yourself to questions from that session.
Again, it's an open forum to troubleshoot,
discuss insights and tensions.
and more broadly, the future of ANA
enablement.
We're a really small group, so just feel free
to unmute yourself and ask your questions.
I don't think we need to raise hands today.
Well,
is Don.
Okay, Don, you go first.
While we're waiting for the first question,
Hayden, what happens when your brain
explodes?
Because I've been kind of feeling that way
with all of the amazing stuff that's been
opening up all over the place.
It's just like really have to contain the
beast a little bit and focus on one thing at a
time and use your notion correctly.
Yep,
sure.
Yeah, I find with like using AI, there's just
so many things going on that even, I just
can't, I find I have to
everything just to close loops on all the
things that I'm doing.
I don't know if you found the same thing.
Yeah, it does help to get Claude to
summarize stuff and refocus stuff and
create some fresh documents.
It helps eliminate the scatter.
But you made a comment about the brain
of the organization.
And so we're kind of speaking to that a
little bit, too.
But I wonder if you want to talk about that
a little bit, about how you see that or what
it means to you, anything.
Yeah, so to me, having a business brain
it's basically having a single, having a
source of information, um, that has all of
the most updated source of information
from your team, which is usually where
most of, um, obviously most of the
information lies.
Um, and then making sure that that's
constantly synchronized across all
platforms.
And then eventually that you have
proactive agents, uh, working with that
information.
So like the master prompt as a concept, is
sort of the first step of a business brain,
right?
And so what you've gone through is
basically like, I would say, a very wide and
shallow snapshot of your brain and how it's
related to the business, right?
But for it to be a business brain, you
actually have to have your team have
probably deeper snapshots to go in.
And then you also need to be able to kind
of make sure that you have a way to refine
and update and identify like divergences
between different people's
brains and snapshots to find a single
source of truth.
And then you need to be able to update
and cascade constantly.
So that last piece is kind of like, how do you
keep the brain up to date?
And so I think keeping the brain up to date
is proactive agents asking people on your
team questions.
It's like a proactive CHRO agent asking if
anyone was hired, fired, demoted,
promoted in the last seven days, as an
example.
So that's kind of the way I see it is like right
now your business brain is a wide and
narrow snapshot of your brain as it relates
to your business.
As you grow this concept, it will take
deeper and narrower snapshots of each
employee's brain as it relates to their role.
There needs to be a process to refine and
identify discrepancies, divergences, what
the actual single source of truth is.
and then a way to kind of constantly
update.
Does that help?
And to keep organizing it, too.
Exactly.
Because, like, when this first came to my
attention, I went, wow, there's so much
wealth in the email files of the
organization.
You know, not accessible to anybody.
Well, you know, I'm just delighted to see I
plugged Claude into my email.
It gives me way better answers than
Gemini when I'm looking for something.
And so if you have an employee able to
access that resource about how to contact
this vendor or the history of this vendor or
whatever, those are the kind of things that
make the organization so much smarter so
fast.
Yep.
And that's a whole other approach that
other businesses have taken too, right?
Which is just have solutions that are heavy
on integrations, right?
So they integrate with your email, they
integrate with
you know, your Asana, they integrate with
absolutely everything, Salesforce, every
CRM, and try to build, automatically build a
knowledge base based on that.
I think that's been actually the more
common approach, as opposed to saying,
like, you know, here's how a business is
individually set up, and let's create sort of
a knowledge base based on the component
pieces of a business.
What I've just noticed thus far, at least, is
that way those kind of rag systems set up
don't necessarily get the information that
you need, um, quite as efficiently.
So, but it's another, it could, that could be
the future.
I don't know yet yeah we're gonna follow
up.
Yeah.
Nancy, did you know what i did i did
i sort of want to just say where i think i am,
it's given that we have this small group and
it follows from what don said, which
You know, I was sure as we started, all
right, I got a Teams program and I still have
all the information of the like hundreds of
documents that were created in June in my
pro account.
And I definitely don't wanna repeat all of
that.
You know, I did a little bit, I brought some
in, I did some comparisons, but I wanna
confirm that your advice is still to go ahead
and do the assessments of each of the
cycles from my brain and make that part of
the project knowledge.
Then what I've been doing I've only put one
really so far into stage three because I've
been sharing with my team the videos and
the slides so that they can be following
along.
is my management team so that when this
course is over, I want to have each of those
leaders kind of do that same assessment,
like you said, and then can compare them.
And I want the, there's like three other
people and me to be our,
enterprise brain.
And I want them to work with me putting it
into stage three so that they feel like
ownership with what you're saying, that
that's a one place of truth and that that's
where we'll update it.
Even though I'm still confused, like, all
right, if I'm updating in stage three and is
the Claude thing still up to date?
And I think you've said something about
them sinking, but I, you know, so that's
kind of my strategy.
I'm, I haven't done all the assessments and
I haven't put them in there, but I'm, Also
like Don, you know, there's so many things
happening in this cloud code and the
possibilities of, you know, it's too exciting
and at the same time exhausting.
But that flow of what's going on, I'd just
like to hear you react to it.
Yeah, I think everything you're doing is the
right thing.
So you're teaching other people, you're
giving them the foundations, you're getting
them bought in.
That's absolutely the right thing.
I agree on the Claude side.
Yes, you should still be going through those
assessments in the separate Teams
account.
In terms of what is up to date and keeping
things up to date, we're not quite there yet.
In a few more sessions, we're going to talk
about what is your single source of truth,
how do you keep that up to date, and then
how do you synchronize everything else?
And so my approach has been stage three
is my single source of truth, and then I
synchronize
with stage three and I synchronize Claude
code with stage three and vice versa.
It means when you're updating in stage
three, it will go back to Claude and.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, so like the way you can do it with a
Google is in Claude as a project, you have a
Google doc as your project knowledge
source, right?
So as opposed to a markdown file, it's a
Google doc.
And then stage three can basically write to
that Google doc,
with the most up-to-date information.
And so that way, as long as Stage 3 is
up-to-date, Cloud is always staying
up-to-date, right?
That's one way to do it.
There's other ways you could do it.
And again, Stage 3 doesn't need to be the
thing.
If you want to like vibe code your own
version of Stage 3 and then have it do the
same thing, that could also work.
So are you saying that we're covering this
in a future session?
Yeah, in the last session.
I think you should speak up and say other
cool things that you're doing because you
really inspired me with the invoice
scanning thing.
Who's this?
Mike.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I think my internet broke up for a minute.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I've been playing around a little bit
with co-work and the last time I talked a
little bit about the invoicing process or
processing of receipts, creating a
spreadsheet.
What we're working on now is our proposal
system.
So our core system doesn't do a great job of
generating proposals.
So I had Claude create a format for those.
And we just give it some core documents
on the desktop, a price list, a customer list
with primary contacts.
And then our managers can just use
whisper flow or something like that and
dictate what we want a proposal to be, and
it makes all the line items, automatically
puts that in a PDF, and then creates a
spreadsheet.
So for us, it's sort of a workaround for what
an ERP might do, but it's actually working a
lot better than what we had.
Awesome.
So I found that with my minimal
knowledge, How much time did the
proposal take before and how long does it
take now?
So what's like the cost collapse for you?
We were just late.
It took us a long time to do them.
And we actually haven't, we just, I mean, I
just, I didn't even finish it yet.
It's basically close to finish.
We have to update our list because we
can't have a close
list of who the primary contact was.
So I ran with not the correct data.
So I don't know yet.
But I anticipate we'll probably save 15
minutes per proposal.
And we do lots of these for irrigation and
enhancements.
So I think each manager will potentially
save one to two hours a week just doing
that.
And we'll be much more organized.
We had things slipping through the cracks
sometimes too, because it's a bit of a
manual process and keeping track whether
it was submitted and then invoiced after it
was done.
So it just ties into our whole workflow
where we can track it better.
Thanks for sharing.
Do you have any questions?
I had a question.
I just wanted to follow up on your mention
of RAG.
And, you know, I guess I would consider
some of the comments you've made before
about using Slack integration to Salesforce
and things like that may be part of the RAG
system.
And what we're doing in the class, more
formally structured,
So would you say that you really consider
the best approach to use both of those,
depending on the circumstances where you
have the more formalized SOPs, but you're
also using a little bit more formal calling
out of data that resides in different areas
so that people can keep up to date on the
knowledge?
And tied to that, I'm also curious why you
decided to build your CRM in Airtable
Because I think you had mentioned last
summer potentially just using Slack to
interact with one license of Salesforce.
Just your thoughts on that.
So on the first question, I'll answer the
second question first because that's easier.
It was actually a different company that set
up the Airtable instance.
I didn't set it up.
One of the people in my leadership team
did.
Um, so it was this company in power labs.
Um, and so we didn't have Salesforce or
any licenses.
Um, and, and he just, I don't know why he
chose air table.
I said, take a look at notion air table and a
few other things, pick and choose.
Um, I am moving actually from, uh, so
Salesforce, obviously big company has like
these minimum licenses and annual
structures.
And so I actually will be, I actually did
cancel my Salesforce account.
I think it's done as of May and I'm actually
moving to that same Airtable integration
because they would not let me reduce it to
one or two accounts.
Hence their stock dying.
As your second question, so
set up a few different things with RAG in
the past.
So I think my comment was, I initially
thought there's this interesting thing as, as
models are coming out so fast and with
such wide improvements that my current
position is that rag may be unnecessary
for, for almost all use cases, simply because
both token windows and like needle in a
haystack benchmarks are just going up and
up and up and up.
And so like all you really need is just
slightly better context management.
So you don't have just ridiculously large
master prompts.
And I've actually found that that's probably
more accurate than RAG and it's like a lot
easier to set up.
And also obviously tokens are getting
cheaper.
So because of that, I would say like RAG
makes a lot of sense in certain use cases
that are
outside of the scope of the standard
curriculum.
For sure, if you want to like set up like a
double of yourself, right?
And you want to feed like, you know, all of
the content you've ever written and then
have turned that into a chat bot that other
people can interact with, 100% you need
RAG for that, right?
Like you can't just tokenize that.
But I think for most use cases, and in your
example of like the Slack Salesforce
integration, originally that used RAG, it no
longer needs to.
Like you could easily do that in, you know,
Zapier, Lindy, even without code.
So I would actually say RAG is now needed
for fairly sophisticated use cases.
And in every iteration of a model that
comes out, I'm seeing it less and less
necessary.
But that's just my experience.
I had to look up that means retrieval
augmented generation.
So we're talking about.
Yeah.
Okay.
Basically you're, you're creating a vector
database based on, and you can, IBM
actually, IBM has a good YouTube channel
on AI and they have some good stuff on
rag.
If you're curious to learn a bit more.
No.
I think a cloud is sufficing for now on that
one.
Yeah.
You're welcome.
Wow.
So I do have another comment if I don't
want to...
Let me just say something, John, about that
rag thing, right?
I just was flipping through and I saw some,
I don't know if he's Dutch, but a guy who
was teaching about Claude Code and how it
worked and what all the stuff was.
And then he says, in case you don't know
me, let me introduce myself.
I am the avatar of this guy, you know, but
he reads every one of your things while I'm
here with you.
He's out there talking, you know, making
more content and answering things.
But it was so realistic and really...
Charlie.
Look
that.
He introduced himself as the avatar of this
guy.
And he says, but he's, he's out there talking
with clients and he will, he will read every
one of your things.
Who was it?
I've been studying AI avatar YouTubes.
All right.
I'll, I'll send the link in here.
I have him saved someplace.
Just, you can go out and I'll find that.
There's another woman who does a Julia
something.
So I have a leadership related question
around, I wanted to invite you to speak a
little bit more about a bottom up training.
So you're asking staff people to describe
their roles and responsibilities and create,
you know, come up with their point of view
on how they, on what they're supposed to
be doing.
Yeah.
So I have, so we have a teams program that
we train teams on
the first
three sessions are very similar to kind of
the first three sessions you guys went
through.
And basically the concept is you're creating
prompts to effectively interview each
person.
And then based on that interview about
certain things, based on that interview,
create certain artifacts that they can add
to their own role master prompt.
And so just like what you went through,
you know, that kind of grows and grows
and grows.
and then goes through an asynchronous
track where that's related to specifically
the processes that they, they work in.
And then they start kind of building out
processes there, and then they build out
the clarity board.
Um, but basically the same, it's the same
concept where they put in prompts into
Claude interact with
Claude creates artifacts that builds a role
master prompt for them.
Right.
And then that surfaces commitments for
process ownership, um, pretty early on
services commitments.
It services AI automation and delegation
opportunities.
It helps them create a prompt library
related to all the things that they work on.
And then basically the end of the first, we
had 13 sessions, right?
Everybody, so we just trained a team of 60
and all 60 of them had like all these
artifacts.
And that goes into basically this kind of
business brain processing period where we
identify, All of the ways that the master
prompt needs to be adjusted.
We identify discrepancies between
different people and what they say about
the organization.
We identify all the biggest opportunities for
AI implementation within the organization
and kind of stack rank them.
So that's the approach in terms of bottoms
up is like, let AI work with each person
individually and sort of bring out these
artifacts of surface opportunities, surface
ideas.
surface process ownership for them.
And then, yeah, put it all together and kind
of stack rank from the bottom down.
Do they come up with their own KPIs?
And then you mentioned how handy the AI
is for nudging people when they're not
meeting the growth expectations and so
on.
I wanted to invite you to say a little bit
more about what that looks like.
So for me, it's mainly Slack integrations.
And So basically Slack integrations, usually
it's within a channel, right?
Someone will kind of add someone in the
channel in order to usually update
something or reply to something.
I haven't had the need to kind of do the
whole sort of manager integration.
because I haven't done this with like large
organizations where like, if you're multiple
levels deep and someone, you know,
doesn't update it, then the manager gets
notified and, you know,
if that happens too many times, you have
an incident report.
I haven't had to do that, but that would be,
I would imagine the next level of it.
But yeah, for me, it's all been Slack just
because that's where we work.
Very interesting.
But yeah, I mean, when you have, you
definitely eliminate a lot of uncomfortable
conversations when you have a system
that's reporting and functioning, people
can see their own numbers.
And when you're, What gets measured gets
done, right?
And so if you're measuring the right things,
then probably humans will tend to be more
productive.
Yeah, just even for a lot of organizations,
just the creation of that clarity board,
which is, again, it's a prompt, right?
It's a long prompt.
Like it's probably a three to four hour piece
of homework that people go through.
But just that helps them identify.
So that session has them create it.
and then
a meeting with their manager and then go
over it with their manager, which creates
all sorts of questions and which are, which
is good.
Right.
And in many, many cases, like there was no
scorecard before at all.
And so scorecard gets created and then the
manager like thinks about it and, you
know, adjust a little bit.
And so that's great to see because it's like a
bottom up scorecard creation as opposed
to this top down one.
Cause we all know how long it takes and
then how quickly they go at a date.
So the idea is for this process, right?
So the clarity board process, which again,
creates these opportunities as well, which
is kind of like your OKRs, your rocks for it
to be actually instigated on a periodic
basis.
Let's call it every 60 days by each employee
from the bottom up, as opposed to from
the top down, which is the way OKRs are
supposed to be built.
in the way rocks are supposed to be built,
but it's often still instigates from
Thank you.
Lots to think about there.
Speaking of the clarity boards, did you
mention that you were going to share
something about that, and did I miss it, or
is that still something we'll be able to see?
Let me check.
I thought I put it in the forum.
Yeah, look in the chat discussion thing, and
there was a very interesting post going up
in here, including the clarity board and the
loom thing, and There's more to learn.
Were you saying, Don, that it's in Circle?
Is that what you were saying?
Yeah, yeah, I believe so.
Josh, yeah, Josh, AI Sales Workflow is here.
Anyhow, yeah, so I was finding amazing
stuff in the discussion thing.
A Loom video showing the overview of
sales management.
think you did a screen share at the end of
the session, but maybe it's worth.
I thought I put it in here.
I will post it right now.
I just posted it.
Yeah, sorry, I thought I had posted it.
I didn't see it there.
And also, you're putting up YouTube videos
on a channel which is under Empower, I
think, isn't it?
I've got a whole bank of them that I have
not published yet because we're still
figuring out ownership of the channel, and
I've been a bit busy.
But yes, they will be going up on the
Empower Labs channel.
probably starting in a week or two.
That's good to hear, Hayden, because you
make great videos.
Thank you.
Come out of the forest and talk to us.
You probably have a man cave in a tree
somewhere.
You can just do it from there.
Pablo, do you have any questions?
Note, Hayden, that I think it's posted in not
the cohort four.
So you might want to migrate.
Oh, okay.
That's why.
Okay.
Thank you.
Sorry, Pablo, go ahead.
I have right now late night in Ukraine.
I was thinking I have to wait, not go to
sleep.
And so I have some questions.
I am struggling with the language because I
don't know English very well.
It's a little bit difficult.
So I use Notebook.LM and I put transcribe
and presentation in Notebook.LM and
make Ukrainian presentation to myself to
understand better.
And then I found it's great source to my
employees.
So I give them
all presentations and explain master
prompt how it works.
So it's, I think, very good idea to everyone
to use it to share this knowledge with their
employers, employees.
And then it's next good idea like Tiago
Forte share his second brain books like
sources from notebook.lm to everyone.
It's very good.
So in this chat, I can write right now
questions.
If I forget something, I can have answers.
And I even make to-do list from each
presentation, what to do.
Maybe some insights, some to-do list.
It's very good life hack.
And I have problems with...
download SOP to stage 3 I don't know why I
put this SOP and press save.
It doesn't save and some lessons don't
have HTML in this stage 3 there are place to
put SOP and HTML.
I have to generate HTML each time?
In like the actual SOP section?
It's usually just Markdown.
That's basically just text.
Should just copy and paste that in.
In the instructions there are save SOP like
this.
Text, save, and then save HTML.
All right.
So are you talking about like importing the
HTML from Claude into, uh, like for a core
process?
Yeah.
Okay.
So, so that's, uh, that's just to import, uh,
basically all of the racy definitions in it's
not really for the SOP.
You can also just chat with the bot.
Um, so you can go to that core process and
you can literally just chat with it and say,
create everything for me.
Um, I just did it and taught to do it that
way, just cause it's predictable.
right, with an import.
But if you want, and anyone here can, feel
free to just chat with the bot and you can
ask it to create all your blueprints, create
all your guides.
It'll batch it for you.
You just make sure when you go to the
chat that you have on the bottom right,
like underneath the chat window, there's a
master prompt.
Make sure you have it enabled.
Just like a little toggle.
Do you want to share your screen and we
can walk through it?
Or do you want to maybe send me a
screenshot?
Whatever you like.
If you have some screenshot, if you can
share, it will be good.
Well, if you want to send it to me in like a
direct message and circle like a screenshot,
I can look at it directly or send it to my
developer if it's a bug or something.
Sure, you don't want to screen share and
then we can all watch?
Unless it's private, I don't know.
Um, Did you understand?
Would you be willing to that you could
share your screen and Hayden could talk
you through and we could watch?
Sure, I can share the second.
second second show
Uh, you see, Oh, this is Ukrainian.
This will be difficult.
So I try to download in the market to lead,
for example.
I open SOP.
Download.
Before it was here, right now it's empty.
I don't have it.
And I make it four times and it's the same.
I can't save it.
I press here save, create.
It's create, but then it will disappear again.
Right now it's here, but after some time it's
disappeared again.
I don't know why.
Okay.
Yeah, I've never seen that happen.
Let
know if it still happens.
For example, I have here one SOP.
And it's also gone.
I don't know how to look at it.
From sales to delivery.
It must be here.
Yes, somewhere is SOP.
The core process should be there, yeah.
But you would have to copy and paste it in
unless you've already, unless you built it
with the AI chat.
Yes, I copied this before here in SOP, but
right now it's not here.
It's not saved.
For example, I write something here.
I press create and save, yes?
Yep.
And it should be here.
But after some time, it will be gone again.
Empty.
Can you go back to it?
Back to this, okay.
SOP is here.
This is like some kind of quantum theory.
Whenever you show somebody a bug live,
the bug suddenly works, right?
Yeah, if it continues, please send me your
account, and I'll look into it.
I've never seen this happen before.
If it saves it as a version, it should never
disappear.
I could imagine if you didn't click Create
SOP or you didn't click Save Changes, then
it might not save.
And the next question, I try to sort
information.
I show you, I sort it like in Google Drive.
Like Tiago Ford has shown.
I try like this.
By these stages.
Maybe you have some examples how to
sort this information, all these archives,
which is best way, simplest.
Because it's very difficult to update and
refresh.
I have Ukrainian language and English, it's
a little bit difficult.
I try even with cowork, give him work to
sort all my files.
So I organize it mainly in stage three.
In Cloud Code, so just in a local directory,
the way I keep my Cloud Code directory is I
have resources.
So I have companies and then under each
company, I have resources, processes,
priorities.
And then under processes, I have separate
folders for each, for the three layers of
process, right?
So strategic planning, customer lifecycle
and enabling processes.
And then under each one, I have market to
lead, for example,
And then under each market to lead, then I
have each of my individual processes.
But I do that in Cloud Code just so I can tell
it where to look if it needs to follow certain
processes.
But that's the way I organize it personally.
And then if I actually want to look at SOPs,
I organize it in stage three just because it's,
yeah, version controlling and everything is
a real pain.
Yes.
Aiden, do you have any companies that
have two languages?
And if so, how...
How do you recommend doing that?
Because most of my staff speaks
Portuguese better than they do English.
So I would just keep probably versions of
the SOP in each language, right?
So you could have two instances in Market
to Lead in stage three, right?
One in Portuguese and one in English.
For example, I open two windows, one
window English, where I copy
paste these prompts, and second, this is
translated Ukrainian.
But I use English.
Put both of those into stage three.
Once you've made that.
In my cloud, I put English version, but it
speaks with me in Ukrainian.
And I always mark with emoji when I go to
the stages to not forget, because Some
stages go in the same time.
One information I give to one person and
second give to another person and wait for
answers.
And it can be two or three days.
So I forget.
So do not forget.
I mark this with emoji.
It's much more easy.
And I found a lot of interesting information
from persons.
They give me answers.
It is different from what I was thinking.
Like it was in theory, but in fact, it was
different.
It's great.
Yep.
And I have one more question.
How your daily work, daily routine looks
like when you work with AI, your standard
work?
So I am typically working cloud code.
I organize myself in Obsidian.
My cloud code controls my Obsidian.
So I have obsidians vaults within my cloud
code directory.
And so that therefore I can use cloud code
to, you know, play with all my notes and
organize everything for me.
Um, I typically will be working on about
three things at a time.
That's sort of the max that, that, that
maximally, uh, rides a line between anxiety
and boredom for me.
Uh, and so I'll have typically three chats on
cloud code running at a time.
So usually, um, maybe I'll be writing
curriculum on in one and then maybe
doing a couple of videos and another, for
example, um, I wake up early.
So I usually start around four 30 in the
morning and usually between four 30 and
eight, like before four 30 and seven 30
before like everyone else wakes up.
Um, I do all of my, um, sort of deep work.
I, and then meetings stuff sort of happen
after that.
Um,
Like I said to Mike or to Don, I find it
challenge, like the most challenging piece,
especially with Cloud Code is just having a
system to actually close loops properly.
So you don't end up working like 15 hours a
day because it's so addictive.
And so usually I just kind of organize
myself in Obsidian.
I've seen some people have kind of their
interesting like AI Kanbans where Cloud
Code actually just updates its own Kanban
for you.
to kind of solve this problem because it's
apparently a common problem.
Yeah, if you use Cloud Code and you use
slash insights, maybe I'll do that once and
share it with the group and you can sort of
see how it gives you this pretty cool
insights across all your sessions on how
you use Cloud Code, what you use it for.
It gives you sort of suggestions on
improvements.
So for anyone who uses Cloud Code and
didn't know that, that's a neat little tip.
Does that answer your question?
Yeah.
I built a second brain maybe one year ago
with Evernote, in Evernote.
It's very good.
I spent maybe five days to build it, and I
have 3,000 nodes and sorted it very well.
I don't know how it works at City, and
maybe it's the same.
But without Evernote, I think it will be
to do this.
Yeah, so I actually, I've been a OneNote
user all my life since about, probably since
about OneNote basically came out.
And I tried to move to Evernote multiple
times and it was finally, it was Cloud Code
that actually got me to move to Obsidian,
which I'm enjoying so far.
But the fact that you can get Cloud Code to,
take like mass batch actions on all your
notes.
It's, it's super useful.
Right.
So you can, you can tell it.
I literally, so I just, when I first started
using obsidian, I just loosely added
everything and probably had like 40 or 50
notes before I finally like said, cloud could
like organize my notes.
Like, and it just did in perfect folders,
everything like, and then I can, I don't have
to like move things around, you know,
every once in a while, I'll just say like
update my notes as a skill and it'll go in and
it'll like
check everything off and add dates and add
tags.
And so that part of it's kind of cool.
If you want to, I guess there's probably
some note, some PKM geeks in here, if they
want to check that out.
Yeah.
just, when I started working in cowork, I, I
never considered obsidian and I've just
been watching videos the last couple of
days because it's on the desktop.
And I'm like, I use notion for that, but I'm
considering moving.
I'm curious if you, I use TickTick for tasks.
My personal task is just loaded with
hundreds of tasks.
But I'm also considering if that's a viable
alternative, putting notes and tasks.
And as an extension of that question, do
you really see software moving back more
to the desktop than the cloud because of
these tools in general?
Like it seems like they're a little more –
there's more –
value on having that on your desktop,
especially marked downwards.
Did Mike cut for anyone else?
Okay.
Yes.
I'll wait until he's back in before I answer.
I came back and turned off video.
I'm not sure.
Did I get cut off in the middle of the
question?
Yeah, you did.
You asked, you were asking about whether
software, if I saw a sort of software going
back to the desktop, did you say anything
after that?
No, that was pretty much the end.
That's a good question.
Probably not.
I mean, temporarily, yes.
But probably not.
If you actually look at most of the functions
that Cloud Code or Coworker are doing, it's
a little faster on the desktop, but it's not
limited to the desktop.
And you're still calling
the API for a lot of different things.
So I think that's probably a temporary
moment in time that we're going to the
desktop for this.
And I don't know how long that is, but I
think people need to probably still create
those solutions.
So me personally, what I'm working on
now, I didn't have to do this until I started
now sharing my cloud code with other
team members.
but basically connecting Cloud Code to
GitHub and then having GitHub act as your
synchronization layer.
So effectively, I had to create a hack
around this in order to
desktop synchronized with Cloud.
But I think that's probably for the next six
months, I would guess, before there's a
more elegant solution.
And I don't think Cloud Code's going to be
the winner necessarily.
Right?
It's just the winner right now.
I was wondering if it was a way to offload
token use, you know, that if you're doing
some of the processing on your own
computer and everybody's doing that, it
might be freeing up your cloud internet to
do stuff.
Yeah, I haven't, I really haven't looked into
exactly what is being used from a, like a
token perspective versus, you know, and I
guess I don't know enough about
programming.
to fully understand that.
I would imagine you're right.
So somebody made a presentation about
how code co-work worked and then they
showed what the cost was per tokens and
that it was a lot less of doing parts of it in
co-work.
Okay, that's interesting.
I know like most of, so one big piece of
what's so useful about
co-work and cloud code is just like the fact
that you can use like grep searches, which
is basically just like regular expressions,
right.
To search anything.
Um, and, and like that, that's something
that I would imagine doesn't use a ton of
tokens and, but is extremely efficient to do
locally.
Mike is asking if you manage your tasks in
Obsidian as well.
I do.
Yeah.
Again, it's new.
I've only moved over to it fairly recently.
I was a OneNote person all my life.
I know it's one of the weaker platforms
now.
Yeah, I did see some interesting examples
of how that can work, and I was just
wondering because I manage in TickTick
and I have a lot of tasks there.
And just coordinating, you know, I can't use
Notion for that.
It's just too messy.
But I am considering doing it all in Obsidian
now.
Yeah, I mean, what I love about Obsidian is
just that it's simple.
Everything is a markdown file, and it's
loaded locally.
And so, again, just using CloudCat, I haven't
probably touched –
1% of what could be done.
So yeah, I definitely check it out.
I have a feeling, I mean, this is actually in
Cloud Code if you go to Cloud as one of the
examples, but I have a feeling it'll become
fairly common where you have like a single
to-do.md, right?
That you're constantly updating, right?
With your today's task, this week backlog,
whatever.
And you'll just tell Cloud Code, like identify
tasks that you can do, right?
On my to-do.
And I think that will be like a pretty
common, and it's probably something that
could work right now, I just haven't really
tried it.
And it would just look through all your
tasks and be like, calculate and be like, I
think I could do like 80% of this task and I
get started, right?
That's great, thanks.
Go ahead, Don.
So I am a little, I need to get clarified on, at
the end of our cohort here, after two
months,
something is going away, right?
We're not going to have access to the login
or what happens?
I, yeah, after two months, the stage three,
um, information goes away.
Um, I'm, I'm happy to keep it going for a
while.
I, again, I've been very loosely or I'm, I'm
unsure what to do with it still.
Um, For now, as long as like the API costs
are low, I'm, you know, probably just
continue to give access.
Right now it's like beta for about 100
people.
But yeah, the idea there was stage three
would eventually become a paid product.
I don't think it's ready yet.
And so I wouldn't charge for it yet.
Okay.
So the curriculum and discussion will all
stay up for a while?
Yep.
Yeah, well, you're also part of the beta
cohort, right?
So you have it for...
long time, right?
Mm hmm.
How
do we have it for?
On the beta cohort?
I think forever, as long as it exists, yeah.
Oh, okay.
That helps.
That was part of the beta cohort thing,
right?
Might be two months.
Yeah.
I see.
Okay, thank you.
Relieves a little anxiety.
Wait, wait, wait.
No.
Okay, great.
final questions or comments before we
wrap up today?
have one more.
Go ahead, Mike.
Go ahead.
Well, I already asked this last week, but I
want to ask Aidan, too.
It's really just about security because I'm
watching a lot of videos and subject
experts in AI.
And most of them seem to say to be
cautious about how you use AI and give
access.
And I've seen some things I like, I don't use
ClickUp, but I like the fact that it's a
security based, like a role based where you
give access and some of the stuff on the
desktop, whether it's, um, cloud code or,
uh, you know, open clot, you know, just for
people who are novices just getting
started, uh,
You know, should we be thinking about
security or setting things up?
Josh kind of felt like, well, AI is coming, so,
you know, don't worry about it too much.
But, you know, I just wonder what the
frameworks are, if you have any way of
thinking about that.
Should we be thinking about it?
So, yeah, you should be thinking about it.
Everything that has
taught thus far has been, you know, pretty
secure, right?
Because you're really just working with an
LLM in a browser.
The more you open, remove permissions
from LLMs, the more risky it gets and the
more useful they get, right?
So that's the trade-off.
So Cloud Code, unless you bypass
permissions in Cloud Code, which you have
to know how to do that, Cloud Code is
pretty safe, right?
Because it...
basically asks you every single time and it's
kind of, it's only exists within that directory
and it can't delete stuff.
Um, and it, it typically doesn't go out and
like message other people and open itself
up to prompt injections.
Open claw is totally different.
And my advice to anyone who's not a
developer is don't touch it.
Um, because of the security risks, but also
because it's like not nearly as easy to set
up and actually be, be made useful.
Um, as, you know, YouTube videos seem to
indicate.
Like I know Tiago said he, ever since he
installed OpenClaw, he's become infinitely
less productive because he's spent so much
time trying to make it work.
So, yeah, I would say the, yeah, just
understand that like the more access you
give AI, right, the more useful it is, but the
more you need to worry about security.
Everything we're talking about, cloud code,
et cetera, I would say it's not that bad.
When you start getting into agents that
start talking to strangers on the web, when
you start installing more skills and stuff
like that, you need to be careful because
there can be prompt injections, either
through other people prompt injecting
when they're chatting with an agent, or if
you install a skill that can sometimes do
malicious things like start mining crypto on
your computer and stuff.
So, yeah, actually, that's two things to
mention.
So one is when you install skills, look at the
skills.
And then there are certain websites like
skills.sh that I think Vercel actually checks
all the time.
Do not check ratings and trust ratings.
Ratings can be completely spoofed already.
on skills, so that is not a trustable signal.
So either look at it yourself or make sure
it's on a marketplace that's maintained by
an organization like Vercel, which is
skills.sh.
If you do create agents, which I don't think
anyone is doing yet here, but if you do
create agents that talk to potential
customers, like a customer service bot, a
sales bot, anything like that, be aware that
what prompt injection is is basically
someone malicious can go and try to get,
you know, internal customer information
or internal company information by just
chatting with the bot.
And so the way to typically overcome that
is that you have another level of agent that
checks every single communication from
your main bot before it goes out, ensuring
that it's not giving up any kind of sensitive
data.
What that ends up doing is it ends up using
twice as many tokens, right?
and twice as many requests, but that's
typically the standard way people are
doing this.
Great.
if you give Cloud Code, it's doing some work
in your browser, and so it's opening a
browser.
I haven't actually paid attention to this, but
my browser typically always has a
password manager that's open.
Like, is there any risk?
So I'm not giving it access to my passwords
per se, They're actually accessible if it's
opening my browser.
We worry about things like that.
Yeah, that's a good question.
I don't know how to answer that.
Um, on the browser side, uh, probably ask,
I would ask Cloud Code what it actually has
access to.
I don't usually use the browser
by the way.
Most things that can be done with a
browser extension can be done with
another skill and actually just slows things
down and probably is a bit of security risk.
But for me, it was mainly just an efficiency
thing.
So if Cloud Code gets you to use the
browser extension, I would actually
have it to find an alternative solution that
doesn't use a browser extension.
All right, thanks.
Well, thanks, everyone.
That was fun.
Thank you.
Nice to see you all.
See you on Monday.
Yeah.
Good night, everyone.
All right.
Have a good weekend.
Bye for now.
Bye-bye.